http://www.icr.org/home/privacy

Dinosaurs and the Bible
More Books...
Privacy Policy
The Institute for Creation Research (ICR) will not give or sell personal information that you enter on our website. In addition, ICR protects our donor information, including information obtained through the website, emails, traditional mail, phone, live events, and/or any other contact. ICR will never share or sell this information with any outside party.
No information is collected by our website other than data that is typically collected by websites in general. If you choose to provide additional information, such as signing up for a free subscription, this will allow us to serve you better.
Any personal information provided to a legitimate agent of ICR (such as to enable mailings or credit card transactions) will be limited to a “need to know” restricted access. Our agents are bound by fiduciary laws to protect your personal information from unauthorized use.
ICR uses audience data from Google Analytics to improve our websites and mobile apps. Click here for more information on managing the data your browser shares with Google.
If you no longer wish to receive our email publications, please click here to unsubscribe. To request removal from our print mailing list, please send your name and postal address to subscriptions@icr.org.
This site is informational and educational in nature. It is not offering professional legal, tax, or accounting advice on your estate. All persons who use information from this site must be advised by qualified professional counsel. For specific advice about your estate, please consult a qualified professional advisor.
If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us.
Return to our subscription form.
